你得说服自己
You have to ask yourself...
这人肯定有夹带
what brought the person
to this point.
看他的表情
他的举止 他的途径
What was seen in his face,
his manner, that channeled him here.
你得确信自己
You have
to convince yourself...
能搜出他所藏的东西
that this person has something hidden
that you have to find.
你检查他的行李袋
但他的表情
You check his bags,
but it's his face...
他的姿势
才是你应该真正注意的
his gestures that
you're really watching.
谢谢你
Thank you.
他瞪着你看
He's staring straight at you.
仔细看他
Look at him, carefully.
你看到什么?
What do you see?
第4保安部17号行李认领处
Security 4 to Baggage Claim 17.
你去哪里?
市中心
Where you headed?
Uh, downtown.
要分摊车资吗?
好呀
You want to split it?
S-Sure.
什么?今晚不行，你确定?
What? Not tonight.
Are you sure?
不能取消吗?
Well, can't you cancel?
这是什么?
Oh. Uh... what are these?
今晚的芭蕾舞票
Ballet tickets for tonight.
哦
Oh.
你不喜欢芭蕾?
只喜欢某芭蕾
You don't like ballet?
Well, some ballets.
那就是某些芭蕾
Well, that's exactly
what this is: some ballet.
你也可以在门口把它卖掉
Look, you can always scalp
the tickets at the door.
你的意思是
作为交换...
Oh, you mean, uh,
take these in exchange...
要用它抵车资
你认为呢?
for you paying your part of the fare.
Well, what do you think?
再见 约翰
晚安 约翰
See ya, John.
Good night, John.
再见
See you guys.
See ya.
克莉汀娜，你来了
赶快换衣服
Christina, here you are.
Hurry and get dressed.
他们都在找你
People are asking for you.
她来了 我找到她了
She's right over there. I'll get her.
再见
Bye.
Yeah!
各位，用力鼓掌吧
Let's bring those big, hairy
palms together, gentlemen...
热烈鼓掌
and have a nice,
big round of applause...
欢迎卡莉
for Kali!
卡莉
Kali.
没错，卡莉
Yes, indeed. Kali.
让卡莉陪你坐台
And you, too, can you, too,
can have Kali come over to your table...
花五块就可以
她会引你进入她的神秘世界
for only five dollars, where she can
show you the mysteries of her world.
相信我，男士们
Trust me, gentlemen. Trust me.
噢！宝贝，宝贝，宝贝
Oh! Baby, baby, baby!
噢！宝贝，为我表演
Ooh! Do it for me, baby!
老天，真不可思议
Oh! My God, that's incredible.
That's incredible.
让我问你们件事，男士们
Let me ask you something,
gentlemen.
是什么使女学生天真无邪?
What is it that gives a schoolgirl
her special innocence?
她的香味?鲜花?轻柔春雨?
Her sweet fragrance? Fresh flowers...
light as a spring rain?
我的天
Oh, my God.
My God.
还是她需要爱抚的结实细嫩肌肤...
Or is it her firm, young flesh
inviting your every caress...
引诱你探索...
enticing you to explore...
她最深处的秘密?
her deepest
and most private secrets?
这点我要你们自己决定
Well, gentlemen, I'm gonna let you
decide that one for yourselves.
让我们一起欢迎漂亮的
Please join me
in welcoming a sassy...
性感宝贝
bit of jailbait
to our stage.
对
Yes, indeed.
出来，可爱的克莉丝
Come out, sweet Chrissy.
不管你在那，出来吧
Wherever you are, baby,
come on out.
你以为你很坏?
You think you're bad, eh, baby?
你是很坏
You're bad.
我要票
That will be $5.50.
谢谢
Thank you.
艾瑞克?
什么事?
Eric?
What?
琳达跳完舞了
Linda finished her dance.
快用你的大手鼓掌 男士们
Let's bring those big, hairy
palms together, gentlemen.
放纵吧 男士们
Give it up. Yeah, gentlemen. Yes.
咱们为琳达鼓掌
Have a nice, big round
of applause for Linda. Yeah.
好呀，琳达
Yes, indeed, Linda.
我想提醒的是
没有比琳达更喜欢做的事情了...
And just a reminder that there is
nothing Linda would love more...
那就是偷溜过去陪你坐台
than to slink over
to your table and...
花五块，就会有私密秀
give you your own private show
for only five dollars.
没错
That's right.
五块就能得美丽的狐狸精
Five dollars is all it takes
to have one of our beautiful foxes...
她会陪你坐台
使你兴奋不巳
come over to your table
and get you all hot and bothered.
为何要烦恼
But, hey, why be bothered...
何不来点帝王享受
when you're being treated
like a king?
累了一天
You've had a rough day.
难道你不该...
Don't you think you owe it
to yourselves to...
做点特别的事?
do something that'll make you feel
like you're someone special?
你很特别
You are someone special.
只要五块钱，便可证明
Five dollars is all
it takes to prove it.
大家为蜜雪儿鼓掌吧
Yes, let's have a nice big round
of applause for Michelle.
天,真美
My God, that was beautiful.
宝贝，出来
Ooh, baby, you come out.
我想提醒的是
没有比蜜雪儿更喜欢做的事情了...
And just to remind you that, uh, there's
nothing Michelle would love more...
那就是偷溜过去陪你坐台
为你一人跳舞
than to come over to your table
and give you your own private dance.
各位好
Hello, gentlemen!
外面有人吗?有人活着吗?
Anybody out there?
Anybody alive?
无论是哪一位，只要花五块，
你就能得到卡莉
Anybody, for five dollars,
you can have Kali.
便可让卡莉陪坐台
Kali at your own private table.
请问，男士们
Let me ask you something,
gentlemen.
女学生为何...
What is it
about a schoolgirl...
天真无邪?
that gives her that
special innocence?
是她们凝视你的方式?
Is it the way that
they can gaze at you...
她渴望你说些话
waiting for you to say something
with so much expectation and hope...
她希望使你陶醉
that you're just...
you're just paralyzed into...
而沉默
into silence?
我要把这还给你
为什么?
Look, uh, I want to give this back to you.
Why?
这些票是别人给我的
Well, you see,
those tickets were given to me...
卖掉它们会我很不自在
and, uh, I just feel uncomfortable
about having sold them.
不要紧
不，真的
That's okay.
No, no, no, really, I-
我们尚未自我介绍 我是汤玛士
We never really introduced ourselves.
I'm Thomas.
大卫
David.
我能用这请你喝一杯?
Can I use this
to take you out for a drink?
你太客气了
但…但什么?
Oh, that's, uh, very kind
of you, but, uh. But what?
但我真的得回家了
But I really have
to get home.
谢了
Thanks.
你下周四有空吗?
Are you available
next Thursday?
我想有吧
好
Uh, I think so, yeah.
Good, good.
崔西
怎样?
Tracey?
Yeah?
我没那么令人烦吧?
I'm not that boring, am I?
什么意思
耳机
What do you mean?
Well, the earphones.
我们曾听收音机
I mean, we used to listen
to the radio...
你常问问题
and you used to ask me
all sorts of questions.
你要我问更多问题?
So you want me
to ask more questions?
当然，如果你想知道什么
Sure. Yeah, I mean, if there's
something y-you want to know.
好，我会想想看
Okay. I'll see
what I can think up.
向你爹问好
我会的
Say hi to your dad.
I will.
晚安
Good night.
有人说什么吗?
没
Did someone say something?
No.
所以怎样?
So, what's the point?
我注意到你的态度改变
I've just noticed
a change in your attitude.
你若不介绍克莉汀娜也行
Look, I would understand if you would
prefer not to introduce Christina.
我可以自己来
I could do it myself.
我想
Actually, I've been thinking
that, perhaps...
我该多参与介绍才对
I should be getting more involved
in the introductions overall.
还能像我妈般有自己麦克风
I could have my own microphone,
like my mother used to do.
不，我很喜欢介绍克莉汀娜
No, I mean, I actually
enjoy introducing Christina.
那对我很有治疗效果
I mean, I find it
very therapeutic, you know?
我不是为此而付钱给你
That's not what you're getting paid for.
Well, it seems to me...
我拿钱是使每位小姐与众不同
that I'm being paid to make every girl
seem like she's something special, right?
所以我得充分运用想像力
So, in order to do that,
I have to let my imagination run wild.
提到克莉汀娜
So, I mean, when it comes
to Christina, I, you know-
我会特别疯狂
My imagination is bound
to run a little wilder.
我无法克制，佐儿
There's nothing that I can do
to control that, Zoe.
那使客人们很不自在
Makes the clients uncomfortable.
你认为你的状况能使人自在?
And you think your state
puts them at ease?
嘿
Hey.
他在踢吗?
Is he kicking?
直如此
All the time.
你想摸吗?
Do you feel like touching it?
哦
Oh.
你觉得如何?
How are you feeling about this?
很好
很好？
Fine.
Fine?
你快乐吗?
Are you happy?
我为你而快乐
For you.
你呢，艾瑞克?
What about you, Eric?
What about you?
我得谨慎处理感情，对吧?
Well, I guess I got to be pretty careful
about my feelings, right?
我的意思是...
I mean, uh...
所以我们才会签合约对吧?
that's why we have
a contract, isn't it?
公寓里到处是灰尘
There's plaster dust
all over the apartment.
不，我没有夸大
昨夜睡觉时都在咳嗽
No, I'm not exaggerating. No, I was
coughing in my sleep last night.
你说我住这儿会很舒服
You told me that it was going to be
comfortable for me to live there...
结果根本不舒服
and it is not comfortable.
家俱上都是灰
There's plastic on the furniture.
真差劲
That is not comfortable living.
噢 过来看看
Yeah. Oh, come on, look.
你说要拆壁纸，不是拆掉墙壁
You told me you were going to strip
the wallpaper, not strip the walls down.
喂，你怎么不早说
Well, no, if you'd,
if you'd told me in the first place-
如果你早说清楚该怎么做
我会考虑
If you'd told me what kind of job
it was, then I would have considered it.
即使是那样，我觉得
你好像犯了错
Although, it's it makes me seem
like you've maybe made a mistake.
那使我感到怀疑
That's what it makes me suspect.
不，太迟了，没办法了
What? No, it's too late now.
It's inaccessible.
我不会付钱给你。干嘛付钱给你？
你事情没做好呀
I'm not gonna pay you. Pay you for what?
You didn't do the job.
你做的不是我要你做的事
Well, you did a job, but it's not
the job that I asked you to do.
不是我们讲好的事
It's not the job
we agreed on.
我可以对任何人做这事
Well, I can get anyone,
any number of people to do this.
对，我无所谓
Yeah, that's just fine with me.
我能效劳吗?
Yeah, can I help you?
品托先生?
是的
Mr. Pinto?
Uh, yes.
我是佛西布朗
我们数周前电话连络过
I'm Francis Brown. We spoke, uh,
on the phone a couple of weeks ago.
加拿大国税局
是的，当然
Revenue Canada.
Oh, uh, of course. Uh-
你旅程如何?
很好
How was your trip?
Oh, it was fine.
你何时回来的?
昨天刚到
And when did you get back?
Um, just yesterday.
天气好吗?
Good weather?
是的，好极了
Yes, yes, lovely. Yeah.
现在有空吗?品托先生?
当然
Is this a good time, Mr. Pinto?
Oh, sure.
但你似乎有点
有点什么?
It's just that you seem a
little, uh，A little what?
心不在焉
不，不
Flustered.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
我很好
I'm fine.
对
Good.
对，我现在不能谈。待会儿
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Listen,
I can't talk to you right now. L-Later.
好，嗯
Okay, uh-
这儿可找到所有银行借贷表?
So this is where I'd find
all the bank s-statements? Uh-
对，好的，还有那些
Yeah, that's right,
and those there.
好，我有问题会再问你
Okay. Well, if I have any questions,
I'll let you know.
是否有点热?
是的
Is it a little hot for you back here?
It's, uh, yeah.
你可开小点
You could turn it down a tad.
我想动物的温度要小心控制
I suppose you have to be pretty careful
with the temperature with the animals.
它们比你想像中更强壮
Oh, well, they're a lot hardier
than you'd think.
我不会认为它很虚弱
I wouldn't think
they're not hardy.
来自异地不表示它们没有耐力
I mean, just because they're exotic
doesn't mean they can't endure extremes.
反正这世界就像丛林对吗?
It is, after all,
a jungle out there, isn't it?
这要多久时间?
Um, so, how long
will this take?
审计?
是的
An audit?
Yes.
看你准备得如何而定
Well, it depends on
how prepared you are.
你有会计师吗?
没有，真的
Have you got an accountant? Uh,
well, um, no. Well, no, not really, no.
真的没有？
Not really?
这要花上阵子了?
也许一天
So this will take, uh, a while?
I could be done by the end of the day.
或要一周
很难讲
Or it might take a week.
It's difficult to say.
好，你若有任何问题
我会告诉你
Oh. Okay. Uh, well, if you have any
questions, um, I'll let you know.
你认识她?
Did you know her?
可以这么说
Sort of.
她曾是你的邻居?
She was your neighbor?
我当过几次她的褓母
I, uh, I baby-sat her
a couple times.
你和她很熟了?
Oh, so you knew her
pretty well, eh?
是的
Yeah. I did.
你呢?
What about you?
我才诉说这件事
Oh, I just, uh, I heard this thing
was being organized, so-
似乎
It seems so, uh...
不像是真的吧?
surreal, doesn't it?
什么?
我们能找到东西
What?
That we'd find anything.
这国家有很多地方可以藏东西
I mean, there's so, uh, many places you
could hide something in this country.
我的名字叫艾瑞克
我叫克莉汀娜
My name's Eric.
I'm Christina.
幸会，克莉汀娜
Hey, nice to meet you,
Christina.
怎样?
Well?
什么怎样?
你不想摸摸看?
Well, what?
Don't you want to touch it?
不必勉强，有的人喜欢这样做
You don't have to. It's one of
those things people normally like to do.
呵
Ah.
艾瑞克怎会称你漂亮的性感宝贝
What is this thing about Eric
calling you "a sassy piece of jailbait"?
就这事?
它会令我不安
What's this thing?
It bothers me.
为什么?
那使你像个小孩似的样
Why?
It makes you out like a child or something.
和我的穿着打扮完全不搭调?
Unlike the tartan skirt and my socks
or the blouse or the way I act, right?
你觉得奇怪吗?
他仍想留下
Do you find it strange that he
would still want to work here?
佐儿，不是人人都可为所欲为
Zoe, not all of us have the luxury
of deciding what to do with our lives.
他是拿人钱财为人办事
It's a job, and he's
getting paid all right.
我觉得这很残酷
I just find it cruel.
开除他呀
So fire him.
算是帮我的忙
As a favor.
你怎能如此漠不关心?
How can you be so detached?
我今天的活干定了
Well, I'm finished for the day.
今天，你还要回来?
Uh, for the day?
Uh, you mean you have to come back?
恐怕是
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
何时较好?
When is a good time?
你不说只要一天?
But, but, I thought you said
it was only going to take one day.
它是只要一天
Well, it can only take a day.
但你的资料放得很凌乱
But you have to understand, you don't
keep very well-organized books.
所以你该找人来帮你忙
That's why you should really think
about getting someone in to help you.
只要一周来一两次
Just somebody to come in
once or twice a week...
视活动的数量及形态而定
depending on the amount of activity
and... the type of activity.
什么意思?
Uh, what do you mean by that?
有些形态或活动更复杂
Well, some types of activity
are more complicated, aren't they?
可能需要较多的心力
It might take more effort
to account for.
哦
Oh.
我在抽屉中找到一把枪
I found a gun
in one of the drawers.
那是我爹的
你爹?
Oh, well, that belonged to my dad.
Your dad?
对，他是防备意外用的
Yeah, I guess he just kept it,
uh, just in case.
防备什么?
防范麻烦?
In case of what?
Well, in case of trouble.
动物会有麻烦?
With the animals?
我周一回来好吗
Would Monday be a good time
for me to come back...
品托先生?
好的
Mr. Pinto?
Oh, yeah.
明天呢?
Well, how about, uh, tomorrow?
明天我有约会
周末前我都很忙的
Uh, I have appointments for tomorrow.
Actually, I'm pretty busy 'til the end of the week.
周一不行吗?
Monday's not good?
不会啊，周一很好
No, uh, Monday's fine.
约十点?
好
Around 10:00?
Yeah, sure.
很好
周末愉快
Well, good.
Have a nice weekend.
奇怪那鸟可能比我们活得久
Strange to think that bird
is probably going to outlive us.
奇怪?
Strange?
你可曾教它说话
Did you ever teach it
to say anything?
有的
Yes.
它说什么，哈洛?
它再也不肯说了
What does it say, Harold?
It doesn't really say it anymore.
它忘了？
It forgot?
我想不是
应该不会忘
I don't think so.
They're not supposed to forget.
大概没兴趣吧
It must have just lost interest.
抱歉迟到了
不要紧，我们刚在谈菲利
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay. We're just talking about Felix.
它怎样?
What about him?
爹?
Dad?
我给钢琴调过音了，音色真美
I had the piano tuned.
It sounds beautiful.
听来如何?
So, how does it sound?
很好
是吗?好
It's good.
Yeah? Good, good.
好，我不会太迟的
怎样是太迟?
Okay, well, I shouldn't be too late.
What's "too late"?
约十一点左右回来?
好
Around 11:00 or so?
Okay.
你要票吗?
You looking for tickets?
对，多少钱?
Uh, yeah. How much?
『我要票』
太辣了
That's too hot.
他每隔一晚都会来
He comes in here every other night.
同样的酒
He has his favorite drink...
坐他的老位子
找他最欣赏的舞娘
at his favorite table
with his favorite dancer.
有时他等她，有时她等他
Sometimes he has to wait for her,
and sometimes she's waiting for him.
她会保护他，她是他的天使
She'll protect him.
She's his angel.
好，各位
表演的时间到了
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
it's show time at the Exotica.
花五块就可...
And just to remind you
that five dollars is all it takes...
找美人儿陪你坐
to have one of our lovely ladies
come over to your table...
她会引导你进入神秘世界
and show you the mysteries
of their world.
你若不兴奋就是麻木不仁了
Now if that didn't
turn you on, gentlemen, nothing will.
咱们为克莉汀娜鼓掌
Oh, let's have a nice, big, warm round
of applause for Christina, gentlemen!
好呀,克莉汀娜
Yes, Christina!
你在想什么?
What are you thinking?
我在想
如果有人伤害你会怎样?
I was just thinking,
what would happen if someone hurt you?
怎会有人伤害我呢?
H-How could anyone hurt me?
如果我不在附近保护你的话
If I'm not there
to protect you.
你永远会在我身边保护我
You'll always
be there to protect me.
天使
An angel.
嘘
Shh.
怎会有人想做那种事?
Why would somebody want
to do something like that?
怎会有人做那种事?
How could somebody even think
of doing something like that?
别担心了
You mustn't worry.
艾瑞克
Eric! Eric!
哦
Oh.
既性感又疯狂
All hot and bothered, yes, indeed.
来为梅琳鼓掌
Let's have a nice, big
round of applause for Melinda.
拿你的钱令我不安
Uh, listen, I feel bad about,
uh, taking your money.
为什么?
门票是别人送的
Why?
The tickets were given to me, and...
我也该免费送人才对
I should have
given them away for free.
那就太蠢了
为什么?
Well, that would have been stupid.
Why?
因为没人会免费送人
Because no one
gives anything away.
你确定吗?是的，我确定
Are you sure?
Yeah, p-positive.
你把我爹当朋友吗?
Do you consider my dad a friend?
你为何问?
只是问问
Why?
J-Just asking.
你把我当朋友吗?
Does he consider me a friend?
很难说
I don't know.
为什么?
Why not?
因为你在附近时他都不太一样
'Cause he always seems
different when you're around.
怎么不一样?
很紧张
Different in what way?
Tense.
那很糟吗?
Is that bad?
我朋友在时我不会很紧张
Well, I don't really like
to feel tense around my friends.
当然
Well, sure, yeah.
我在这年纪时也如此
I didn't like to feel tense around
my friends when I was your age either.
但你现在会紧张
But you do now?
这不是喜欢与否的问题
No, it's not a question
of liking it or not.
事情就是如此
It's just something that happens.
为什么?
Why?
嗯
Um...
长大后
well... as you get older...
你会了解朋友和自己
you become aware that the people
you meet and the person you are...
都有数量不等的包袱
um, as carrying
a certain amount of baggage.
这包袱会制造紧张
And, and that baggage
creates tension.
你要怎么办呢?
So what do you do about it?
你可以假装它不存在
Well, you can pretend
it's not there...
或是选择不交朋友
or you can choose
not to have friends...
或承认它，继续交朋友
or you can acknowledge that
it's there and have friends anyway.
像我爹?
Like my dad?
对
Right.
我爹和你在一起时我不喜欢他
I don't think that I like my dad
when he's around you.
嗯
Hmm.
喂，那是...
Well, that's...
因为他和我一起时不像他自己
because your dad doesn't like himself
when he's around me.
但那无所谓
But that's okay.
朋友间常会如此
That's... part of what friends do
to each other.
晚安晚安
Good night.
我刚毕业
I, uh-
I just graduated.
真的，我也是
Really?
So did I.
念什么?
无线电通讯?
Oh, yeah? In what?
Radio communications.
你作些什么呢?
那是我想作的
So, so is that what you do?
That's what I'd like to do.
作自由节目主持人
Uh, I do a little
freelance deejay stuff...
但现在我只开计程车
but, you know, right now
I'm just driving a cab.
我想你就是作那种事的
开计程车?
I thought you might do something like that.
Drive a cab?
不，做与用嗓子有关的事
为什么?
No, do something where, you use your voice.
Why?
我不知道，因为你的声音好听
I don't know why.
Because you're easy to listen to.
因为我的声音?
Because of my voice, eh?
我需要找个合适的环境
I just need to find
a structure, you know?
你的意思是?
What do you mean?
我浪费好多时间
时光飞逝
Listen, I waste so much time, you know?
I just My days just slip by, you know?
时光本来不就会消逝吗?
Isn't that what days are supposed to do?
Yeah.
你想做事就不希望如此
Not if you want to make
something of yourself, you know?
你想做什么事呢?
What do you
want to make of yourself?
我不知道，我就是有这想法
I don't know. I just feel that I was
meant to do something with my time.
否则我不会这样想
I mean, otherwise, I wouldn't be
thinking of this this way.
顶多只会继续做已经做的事
I'd be able to just
continue what I was doing, you know?
你有很多朋友吗?
Do you have a lot of friends?
没有，你有吗?
Not really. Do you?
没有
No.
Yeah.
你想过会需要位朋友吗?
Do you ever feel like you need a friend?
有时会
Yeah, sometimes.
何时?
When?
像是现在
Like right now.
为什么?
Why?
因为我遇见你
'Cause I just met you and...
我有话想说
I just feel like
telling someone, you know?
不行，不行
No way.
No way, no way.
嗨
Hi.
老天
怎么回事?
Jesus.
What's the matter?
怎么回事?
她的假发 她的服装
"What's the matter?"
Her wigs, her clothes.
有时我真想把它们扔掉
Sometimes I just feel like
throwing them all away, you know?
你在找什么，佐儿
What are you looking for, Zoe?
你准备把未来寄托在这上面?
我的未来?
I mean, is this where you see your future?
My future?
俱乐部?
The club?
妈死后我只想把这地方卖掉
When Mom died, my immediate idea was
to get rid of this place. Just sell it.
从未想过我会对它感兴趣
为什么呢?
I never thought it would have any interest for me.
So why did it?
我小时侯非常害羞
I used to be very shy
as a child.
我会花数小时看着母亲
I used to watch
my mother for hours...
仰慕她的自由奔放
just admiring
her sense of freedom.
所以机会来时我会接受挑战
So when the opportunity came up,
I thought I would take on the challenge.
你宁可接受她的建议?
So you feel better about adopting her
options rather than creating your own?
我也有自己意见
I have created
my own options too.
我知道
Oh, I know.
这是你和艾瑞克对孩子的合约
It's your contract
for the baby with Eric.
我找到的
I found it.
他知道吗?
Does he know?
希望如此
I would hope so.
否则他会以为我故意讨厌他
Otherwise he might just think I'm
disgusted with him for no particular reason.
我迫切地需要这孩子
Look, I really desperately
needed this child...
艾瑞克很合作
and it just worked out
with Eric.
我并没有伤害你的意思
I didn't mean
to hurt you.
我记得你母亲建这玄关的事
You know, I remember
when your mother built this hallway.
她是为一位常来的富人而建的
She, uh, she built it for this
very rich man who used to come here.
看我们跳舞令他兴奋
所以他付钱请她
He used to get off watching us dance for
other guys, so he actually paid her...
建了这个特殊的地方
方便他来看我们
to construct this very special place
that he could watch us from.
你母亲从未告诉我们那事
Your mother never told us that.
她说它是用来保护我们的
She said it was
to protect us...
便于看管
so she could patrol things.
我一直相信
And I believed her.
直到艾瑞克揭穿
Until Eric told me the truth.
你为何相信他?
Why did you believe him?
我作了选择
I made a choice.
艾瑞克承诺我保证他绝不说谎
And Eric promised me
he'd never lie to me.
怎会有人
How could anyone...
伤害你?
hurt you?
把你从我身边带走?
Take you away from me?
怎会有这种人?
How could anyone?
这是什么机器?
What's this machine?
是孵卵器
Uh, uh, it's an incubator.
干什么用的?
你认为呢?
Wh-What's it for?
Well, what do you think it's for?
孵蛋的 没错
Eggs.
That's right.
是你的蛋?
Are they yours?
什么意思?
Wh-What do you mean?
你不是该坐在上吗?
I mean, shouldn't you be sitting on them or something?
Oh, yeah.
我想我是放弃了巢
Well, I guess
I've abandoned the nest.
里面是什么?
What's inside of them?
蛋？
是的
Uh, the eggs?
Yes.
金刚鹦鹉
Well, uh, Hyacinth Macaws...
如果你想知道的话
if you want to know
the absolute truth.
从那里弄来的?
And where did you get them?
很远的地方
From... very far away.
要试试她?
Hey, check her out, eh?
试试她吧
I said check her out.
你在跟我说话?
Yeah.
You talking to me?
对，我跟你说话
Uh, yes,
I'm talking to you.
试试谁?
What? Check who out?
为你跳舞的女郎
The babe that's dancing
for you, man.
你为她花了不少钱
You've given her quite a run
for your money, man.
什么意思?
What do you mean by that?
她整晚都在为你跳舞
She's been dancing for you all night.
Yeah.
不只是今晚，还有别的夜晚
Yeah, and not just tonight. I mean, I've
noticed you with her other nights too.
你常来这儿?
You come in here all the time or-
对，常来
Uh... yeah.
All the time.
有片子看，你知道的
好
This Visuals, you know?
It's good.
可是
But, uh...
她似乎对你有点兴趣，对吗?
she seems to have a bit
of a thing for you, doesn't she?
我们处得来
We, uh... get along.
我想是朋友
I'm sure you do, my friend.
你们谈什么?
What do you two
talk about, huh?
一般的事
Oh, just, uh...
the usual, I guess.
一般?
The usual?
我想不是如此吧
I don't think you're talking
about what I would call "usual. "
为什么?
因为我看得出来
Why not?
Because I can tell.
你很专注
You get pretty intense,
my friend.
我想我是那样
Well, I guess that's
just the way I am.
你何不摸摸她?
So, uh, Hey, wh-why don't you
give her a little touch, huh?
客人不应该摸的
对，但她喜欢，相信我
You're not supposed to touch.
Ah, but she is into it, believe me.
Yeah.
你怎么知道
大家都知道，老兄
How do you know?
Everybody knows, man.
相信我，朋友
Trust me, my friend.
相信我，摸一下
Trust me.
Just a little touch.
不必太夸张
Nothing too drastic.
你会有美妙经验
Then you will get
the full experience, my friend...
你会喜欢的
and you will love it.
你会喜欢的，你会的
You will love it. Okay?
我摸她会出什么事?
And what happens
when I touch her?
出什么事?
What happens?
离开这儿
出去
You're outta here, man!
Get out!
进来
跪下
Come on.
Get down there.
进来 走吧
Come on. Go.
嗨，你在搞什么鬼
别挡在路中央
Hey, what the hell you doin'?
Get off the road!
走
Move!
什么事这么好笑?
What's so funny?
这像爱抚一只大猩猩
It's like pettin' a gorilla.
喂
Well-
你父亲有这么多毛吗?
Was your father this hairy?
没有，我是从母亲处遗传来的
No, I, uh, I got it
from my mother.
从我母亲家族那里
I mean, I mean,
from my mother's side of the family.
人通常自母系遗传到毛发特徵
That's where you, um,
inherit hair patterns.
我舅父是秃子
你妈的兄弟?
My uncle's bald.
On your mother's side?
对
Mm-hmm.
我谈的是一般的情形
Well, um, I guess I'm talking
about usual patterns.
有时也有例外
Hmm.
There's always exceptions.
这是
That's-
通常都是如此的
That's the way these things... work.
你不是该到医院去?
Shouldn't you go
to the hospital?
不，我很好
No, I'm fine.
你看来不好
You don't look fine.
别担心我，对不对?
You worry about me, don't you?
你认为这很正常?
You think this is normal?
什么?
我们做的事?
What?
What we do.
我们做了什么?
What do we do?
我们从不谈它
That's just it.
We don't speak about it.
你知道那感觉，崔西
You know that feeling
you get sometimes, Tracey...
你不是自愿来到这世界的?
that you didn't ask to be
brought into the world?
是的
Yeah.
谁又是呢?
Well, then who did?
什么?
What?
你自问是不是
If you think that
you didn't ask...
自愿出生的
to be brought
into the world...
谁又是呢?
then who did?
没有人会问你是否自愿来此
All I'm saying is nobody asked you if
you wanted to be brought into the world.
你就是来到这世界
You just ended up getting here.
问题是你既然来了
So the question is,
now that you're here...
谁又要你留下呢?
who's asking you to stay?
谢谢
谢谢你
Thanks.
Thank you.
你确定你没事?
Look, are you sure
you're gonna be okay?
是的
Yes.
晚安
Good night.
他摸了你?
他不想如此做的
He touched you?
He didn't want to.
什么意思?
我了解他
What do you mean?
I know him.
我们都知他为你狂
不是那样的
We all know him. He's crazy about you.
Not like that.
何不找人处理这事，艾瑞克?
Why didn't you get one of the boys
to handle this, Eric?
因为我没用头脑想
Because I didn't think of it.
我看到他摸她，我就
I just saw him touch her, and-
你为何不叫他离开?
Why didn't you
ask him to leave?
他不会听的
你怎么知道?
Because he wouldn't have listened.
How do you know that?
他只活在他自己世界里
Because he's in his own world,
the ass-wipe.
我不知你俩怎么回事
I don't know
where you're both coming from.
你说他摸你，但实际上没有
You are telling me that he touched you,
but he really didn't.
你说你反应过度别无选择
And you're saying that you overreacted,
but you didn't have a choice?
我没有
为什么?
I didn't.
Why not?
为什么?因为他摸了你
Because he touched you.
好了
Okay.
我想知道他说的否有理
All I'm concerned about
is if he makes a case...
我得知道事情经过
I have to know
what happened.
我们告诉过你过程了，佐儿
We told you
what happened, Zoe.
那是过程?
And that is what happened?
对
Yeah.
Okay.
好，谈完了吗?
Is that it?
这是汤玛士
Hi. This is Thomas.
我现在不在，在城里
I am not in at the present time,
but I am in town.
请於『哔』声后留话
Please leave a message
following the beep.
早安
Good morning.
你没起床就不会看到做的
You're probably not up yet,
so you haven't seen what I've done.
我是机场关员
I'm a customs officer
at the airport.
我的确看到你取走了待验的提包
Actually, I saw you the other day when
you were having your bags inspected.
我知道你如何走私这些蛋
I knowI know how you probably
smuggled those eggs in.
我们有特别单位
我想他们将它们送到动物园了
There's a special unit at work. I think
they give them to the zoo or something.
他们问我来源，我只好说谎
They asked me where I got them.
I had to lie.
它们在那?
Where are they?
我拿走了
在哪里
I took them.
Where?
我想再见你 不
I'd like to see you again.
Oh, no.
它们绝对在国内
Uh, no, they're in the country now.
Uh, they're definitely in the country.
现在不在我身上，但在我这儿
It's just I don't have them, uh, with me
presently, but it doesn't mean I can't get them.
只要你给我
And if you can give me, like,
uh, just, uh, um, a couple-
早安
好，我在这儿
Good morning.
Hi. Uh, and, uh, I'm here. Okay.
我们以后再谈
So I'll call-
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
你看来比我更糟糕
You look like you're
in worse shape than I am.
你怎么回事?
Uh... what happened to you?
我从楼上摔下来
Oh, I fell down
some stairs and-
你没事?
我看起来像没事?
Are you okay?
Well, do I look okay?
不，不尽然 我比外表更健康
我给你弄了杯咖啡
Uh, no, not really. Well, I'm better than I look.
Here, I got you a coffee.
你要怎么喝
I didn't, uh-
I didn't know how you took it.
纯的就好
Oh, black's fine.
Oh.
我加了奶精
那也行
Uh, I added cream.
Oh, that's okay.
喝我的 不，我坚持
不，真的
No, here, have mine. No, I insist.
No, really-
这是什么?
What is it?
这里面也有奶精
Well, it's just that
this has cream in it too.
这是牛奶
It's milk.
很好
Oh. Oh, good.
好，好，我要-
Okay, well, I'll, uh-
我要工作了
I'll get to work.
嗯，什么
Mmm, what?
是什么呢?
What is it?
什么使女学生天真无邪?
What is it that gives a schoolgirl
her special innocence?
是她们的气味?
Is it the way they smell?
她们和香水或头发的气味
The sweet smell
of their perfume, of their hair?
鲜花的香气
The aroma
of fresh flowers...
没破坏的身体
and all that other stuff
that hasn't been fucked up...
被通宵及坏食物
by late nights
and a lot of bad food.
是她们的姿势?她们的动作
Is it their gestures...
and the way they move?
她们身躯展现的自尊
The way their body still holds on
to some semblance of self-respect and...
及端庄?
and dignity?
还是她们的玉腿
When they wrap
their beautiful legs around you...
紧绕着你
她看着你
tight and holding on,
looking at you...
你看她们
you looking at them.
这只是
It's just-
还是她们樱桃小嘴吐出的话?
Or is it whatever comes out
of their cute little mouths?
那些问题及怀疑?
All those questions,
all that wondering that-
她们仍有一大段人生待走
It's just, you know, you
They got their whole lives ahead of them, you know?
而你却巳虚掷大半光阴
And you've wasted
half of yours away.
该死
Damn.
是什么?
What is it?
我有时有这感受
There's this feeling
I get sometimes, you know?
什么感受?
What sort of feeling?
我永远无法得到满足
That I wasn't ever meant
to be satisfied.
对什么满足?
Satisfied with what?
对许多事物
A lot of things.
我的意思是，每次我...
I mean, it seems to me
that every time I'm about to...
要抓住某物或某人时...
you know, get a hold
of something or someone...
总会失之交臂
it's just bound
to slip away.
也许你希望机会错失?
Maybe you want it
to slip away.
也许我希望机会错失?
Maybe I want what
to slip away?
你就快拥有的物或人
The things that you think
you're about to have.
你怎么会这样想?
What would you
think about that?
是作为笼统的哲学思想...
As a general philosophy...
还是去让它适合你呢?
or how it pertains to you?
你能谈它与我的关系?
You think you could talk
about how it pertains to me?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我觉得我想要你
Well, I feel
like I want you.
那表示你会离开?
Do you think that means
you'll slip away?
爹?
Dad?
我不要为佛兰西作褓母
I'm not going to baby-sit
for Uncle Francis anymore.
褓母?你是去练习钢琴的呀
Baby-sit?
You go there to practice.
那真荒谬
That's absurd.
为什么?
Why?
爹，他假装我仍为他当褓母
Dad, he pretends
I'm still baby-sitting for him.
你怎会那样想?
Why would you think that?
因为他付钱给我
Because he's paying me.
看房子
To house-sit.
一小时廿元?
Twenty dollars an hour?
何时涨价的?
When did it go up?
他想假装莉莎仍在那儿
He wants to believe
that Lisa's still there.
我等於在帮他欺骗自己
I make it easier for him
to convince himself.
佛兰西常用古怪的方法欺骗自己
Francis always had strange ways
to convince himself...
在许多事情上
of many things.
幻想从未发生的事和可能事
Things that never happened,
things that might happen.
幻想别人做了什么事
People who did things
for reasons, but they didn't.
这跟我何干，爹?
What has any of this
got to do with me, Dad?
无关
Nothing.
完全无关
Nothing at all.
那我为何一直得去?
So why do I have
to keep going there?
你不必去
You don't.
你会告诉他?
And you'll tell him?
那晚那家伙被赶走时我在这儿
I was in here the other night
when that guy was thrown out.
为何发生?
他曾被赶出去吗?
Why did that happen?
Has he ever been thrown out before?
你想他为何摸你?
Why do you think he would touch you?
他的脑中闪过什么念头?
Well, what do you think
was going through his mind when he-
或他在想什么?
Or-Or what was he thinking?
什么事这么好笑?
Well-
What's so funny?
这是个笑话，对吗?
Well, this is a joke, right?
完全不是
Not at all.
你帮我忙我就帮你
If you do this favor for me,
I'll do that favor for you.
但我没隐藏什么?
But I'm not hiding anything.
汤玛士，你在隐藏走私行动
Thomas, you're hiding
a smuggling operation...
它每年获利廿万或更多
that brings in over $200,000 a year,
probably a lot more.
我们怀疑你好久了
We've suspected you
for a long time.
我只是证实巳知的事实
I was just brought in to confirm
what was already known.
你要我怎样回报?
So how do you want me
to report back?
我只要求帮个小忙
All I'm asking
for is a bit of help.
仅此而已
That's all.
知道这些事是很重要的
代我问她这些问题
It's very important for me to know these
things. Just ask her these questions.
替我做这事你就可重新作人
Do this for me,
and you have a clean slate.
今天我真是倒霉
This really hasn't been my day.
改变一切让今天运气转
So change things.
Make it your day.
坐在舞台前的男士们
我能看到你们
And all you men sitting
near that stage, I can see you.
我知道你们的想法
I know what you're thinking.
你们想因为我离舞台最近
You're thinking that "because I'm
sitting next to that stage...
我和花钱者一样享受
I'm getting the same feeling
as all those guys...
既然已经为你们的私人舞女花过钱
shoveling out that cash
for their own private dancer. "
你们若只想看不如去看电影
Well, you know, you guys want
to watch, go to the movies.
这儿可真刀真枪现场表演
We're in the live-action
business here, gents.
那美女在你面前扭动
And, okay, granted
Granted, that beautiful creature writhing before you on stage...
她也许向你笑
she maybe, you know, smiles at you.
对你抛媚眼
She winks her eyes at you occasionally...
你也许自觉像男人
and you may feel like the man.
你们只想要那样?
Is that all you guys
are looking for?
还是全都要？
别这样
Is that all you want?
Come on, come on.
请一位美女到你面前表演
Invite one of our lovely ladies over
to your table where the real action is.
嗨
Yeah!
Hi.
抱歉花了这么久时间
I'm really sorry that took so long,
or I took so long.
今晚真忙
Hi.
It's such a busy night.
我是克莉汀娜
Hi. I'm Chrissy.
嗨，我是汤玛土
Hi. I'm Thomas.
幸会，汤玛土
喜欢这名字
It's nice to meet you, Thomas.
I like the name Thomas a lot.
谢了
Oh, thanks.
你是外地人?
Are you from out of town?
是的
Yes.
你来自何处?
Where are you from?
旧金山
Um... San Francisco.
你开玩笑?我爱旧金山
Oh, you're kidding.
I love San Francisco.
你去过那儿?
Oh, you've-
You've been there?
对，几年前我和大辨论队去过
Yeah, I was there a couple of years ago
with my debating team.
你的辨论队?
Debating team?
Mm-hmm.
对
我崇敬会辩论的人
Um, that's. I admire
someone who can debate well.
我是说辩论，不是耍嘴皮
I mean, who can debate
instead of just argue.
任何人都会耍嘴皮
Well, anyone can argue, but it's
a good skill, uh, discipline...
辩论不同
to be able to debate
and stand back.
它在实际生活上也用得到
Um, and that's something
you can apply in your life...
在学校外面
outside of school.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
当你碰见某人，或谈判时
And, and when you're meeting
someone or negotiating.
谈判?
如果有此需要的话
Negotiating?
Well, I mean, if you have... If you have to...
这是一项很有用的技能
Um, it's a good skill to learn,
as opposed to cheerleading or-
那正是我说的
Well, that's what I say.
别紧张，汤玛土
Don't be nervous
about this, Thomas.
我们来找乐子，好吗?
好呀
We're gonna have some fun, okay?
Sure.
好
嗯
Um... um...
那晚我在这儿
I was here
the other night, um-
哪一晚?
What night was that?
那家伙被赶出去那晚
The night th-that guy
was thrown out.
你正为他跳舞?
You were dancing for him.
他叫佛兰西
His name is Francis.
出了什么事?
Um... what happened?
他是坏孩子
He was a bad boy.
什么意思?
Wh-What do you mean by that?
What do I mean?
你以前常为他跳舞吗?
I mean, have you danced
for him before a lot?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
他可曾被赶出去过?
没有
And has he ever been thrown out before?
No.
那你想出了什么事?
So what do you
think happened?
他摸我
He touched me.
跳舞时客人...
And when you're dancing
for the customer...
不能动手摸的
they can't touch.
对，但他昨晚为何摸你?
Yes, but why do you think
he touched you last night?
他摸过你吗?
Has he ever touched you before?
你花五元就要谈过个吗?
Is this what you really want to talk
about for five bucks a dance, Thomas?
我只想知道，你想他是怎么了
Well, I just want to know
what you think was going on in his mind.
你是来开心理研究会吗?
Are you here for some kind
of psychology conference?
嗯，喂，嗯，是的
Uh, well, uh, yes.
是的，事实上我是
Uh, I am, actually.
他是-
He's, uh-
他是个很特别例子
He's a very particular case.
怎样特别?
Particular in what way?
你想知道全部经过?
Um...
you want the full story?
当然
Sure.
他女儿几年前被谋杀了
His daughter was murdered
a couple of years ago...
他受到牵连
and then he was implicated.
为那命案?
对
For th-the murder?
Yeah.
为什么?
我不知道细节
But why?
I don't know. I don't really remember the details.
后来他无罪获释真凶也被捕
I mean, he was cleared, and then
they caught the guy who did it.
但此事显然
But... it obviously had,
like, this...
对他造成极大影响
this incredible effect on him.
我的意思是
I mean, he is-
他被此事弄得不太正常
He's just so fucked up about it.
哦
Oh.
你知道
You know...
汤玛士
Thomas...
佛兰西和我拥有极特殊的关系
Francis and I have
a very special type of relationship.
我并不介意
And I've never-
I've never minded.
但他违反了规矩
But then he chose
to violate it.
怎样特殊?
S-Special in what way?
我们之间有谅解
Well, we've, we've always
had this understanding.
我为某些事而需要他
I mean, I need him
for certain things...
他为某些事而需要我
and... he needs me
for certain things.
就是如此
I mean, that's the way it's been.
他如何违反规矩?
Uh, and how did he
violate that?
他没做到他该为我演的角色
He-He violated that in his-his, in his
role and what he was supposed to do for me.
他干了什么 为什么
Wh-What's he s... Why?
他该为你作什么?
他来俱乐部他付钱给你了呀
What's he supposed to do for you? I
mean, he comes to this club. He pays you.
因为我为他服务
Because I was
doing things for him...
他为我作事
and he's done things for me.
他为你作什么?
What has he done for you?
我
I'm-
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
对不起，这真蠢
Okay, this is really stupid.
我为何因他摸我而激动
And then I'm getting so emotional
over the fact that he touched me...
我因为他说付钱给我
because, I mean, he was,
he was always paying me...
叫我帮忙
to do him this favor and-
帮什么忙?
我不知道!
What favor?
I don't know, Thomas.
你为何想知道?
我只是
Why do you want to know all this?
Well, I'm sorry, but I, uh-
女学生为何能展现天真无邪?
What is it about a schoolgirl that gives
her that special innocence, gentlemen?
那是你完全无法控制的
Such a thing that you have
absolutely no control over.
以前没有
You never have.
将来也不会
And you never will.
请克莉汀娜出场
他不该那样做的
After this break, we'll be right back with sweet Chrissy...
He not supposed to do that.
谁会帮我回答这个问题
做什么?
who'll help us answer that question.
Do what?
他不该那样做
He's not supposed to-
He's not suppose-
他从座位上可看到我和人谈话
He can obviously see from his booth that
I'm sitting here talking with a client.
我和客人谈话时他不该叫我
He's not supposed to call me
when I'm talking with a client.
你得走了吗?
Why? Do you have to go now?
对
Uh, yeah.
但我要回来再谈
But I want to come back,
and I want to, you know, talk.
但我要到楼下，我不喜欢这儿
But I want to move downstairs.
I don't like it here.
好，好
Sure, sure, sure.
好，回头见
Okay. I'll see you soon.
我得上厕所去
Uh, I'm going to move
to the washroom.
我看到你和那女人一起蛮久的
Hey, I've noticed you've been spending
a lot of time with that lady.
你在和我说话?
Are youAre you talking to me?
对
Yeah.
你俩似乎一见如故
You seem, uh, to, to both
hit it off together.
大概是
Well, I guess.
Yeah.
大概是这样吧
Um, I guess
that can happen.
你们谈什么?
So what do you guys talk about?
谈事情
Oh, just things.
什么事情?
What sort of things?
随便谈谈?
Oh, this and that.
随便谈谈，呃?
"This and that," eh?
真奇怪
You know, it's amazing how...
人能一见如故，对吧?
you can hit it off with someone
like that, isn't it?
你可曾发现有人进入你生活
Have you ever noticed that
some people just drift into your life...
就是好朋友一样?
like you've known them forever?
有的人你能记得
I mean, there are some people
that you can remember...
一见就记得
the moment that you met them
really clearly.
也有人
And other people that...
刚见面就像多年老友
虽然其实没见过面
it seems like you've known them forever,
even though you haven't.
他们成为你持续的记忆
And they all become part of this
continuous memory you have of yourself.
这种持续
This ongoing-
这你在听吗
Are you with me?
对，我想是吧
Uh, yeah, I think so.
我是说
I mean, here you are,
y-you know...
你和她有段美妙的谈话
you're having this beautiful
conversation with her.
你们开始了解对方
You're getting to know
each other, and-
但还有别人来这儿
I mean, there's other guys
that come in here.
有种人每隔几晚就来一次
There's this one guy who comes in here
every other night or something...
他跟她在一起数小时
and he spends
a few hours with her.
但他从来未真正了解她
But he never really
gets to know her, you know?
你没办法
你们俩没办法
Not the way you have.
Not the way you two-
她和你在一起似乎较自在
She really seems
to be herself with you.
你怎么知道?
Well, how do you know?
她较自在?
What? That she's being herself?
对
Yeah.
因为我曾是她的爱人
Because I used to be her lover.
对不起，我不能让你进去
I'm, uh, sorry, sir.
I can't let you in.
为什么不能?
Look, why not?
我能否和经理谈谈?
Look, can I... Can I at least
just talk to the manager?
你要和经理谈?
对对
You want to talk to the manager?
Yeah.
你得了解我们有严格的规定
You have to understand that
we have very strict rules...
对于此类事情的反应
regarding
this sort of behavior here.
我一直都很尊重
但这一次你没有
And I have always respected them.
And this one time you didn't.
问题是这次
Now, the problem, Mr. Brown,
is that this one time...
满屋子的人看着
happened in a room full
of other men who were watching.
如果我让你回俱乐部去
Now, if I let you
back into the club...
谁能阻止他们依样画葫芦?
我说过
what's to stop them from trying to do the same thing?
I told you.
是有人叫我这样做的
我就做了
Someone told me to do it.
I was set up.
你这么容易相信别人?
And you believed that someone?
这是保安部门，请坐下
This is, uh, Security.
Please, sit down.
谢谢
Thank you.
你为何摸她?
Why did you touch her?
我想要弄清楚
为什么？
Well, I needed to make sure.
Why?
如果她允许你呢?你会怎么做?
What if she let you?
What would you have done?
我会很失望
I'd have been disappointed.
我不了解你的话
I'm not sure...
I understand you.
那不是她被教导的方式
That's not the way
she was raised.
你真的认识她?
You know her?
Personally?
我可以介绍你去别的俱乐部
There is another club
I can recommend.
我需要来此地
I need to come here.
我非常了解
不，我想你不了解
I understand that very well.
No, I don't think you understand.
这儿是个特别的地方
Exotica is a special place.
我母亲当初是想创造特殊气氛
My mother was dedicated to creating
a very particular type of atmosphere...
我想维持这一特点
and I would like
to maintain that.
你不明白
You don't understand.
布朗先生我们了解你的遭遇
Mr. Brown, we're all aware
of what you've gone through.
你受了不少罪
You've suffered a lot.
但你得了解此地系提供娱乐
But you have to understand
that Exotica is here for your amusement.
我们提供娱乐，不是治疗
We're here to entertain,
not to heal.
别的地方提供治疗
There are other places for that.
其他地方?
Other places?
我可以给你份名单?
I can give you a list.
布朗先生?
Mr. Brown?
你在听吗
布朗先生?
Are you listening to me,
Mr. Brown?
嗯
Um...
我刚在厕所见个家伙
um, I just met this man
in the washroom.
什么人?
What man?
我不知道，我在里面
Well, I'm not sure.
I was in a booth.
我没机会看见他
I didn't really have
a chance to see him.
你怎样遇见他的?
他开始跟我说话
So how did you meet him?
He just started talking to me.
说什么?
And what did he say?
他说他曾是你的爱人
Well, um, he said
he used to be your lover.
这总是个悲伤的时刻
Well, it's always
a sad moment, gentlemen...
时钟响后
when that clock
strikes that magic hour...
我们得送你返回夜里
and we have to send you out
into the long and dark and lonely night.
但记住
But just remember...
我只有一梦之隔
we're only ever
just a dream away...
无论在哪
wherever that is.
我该走了
I guess-
I have to go.
哦，好的
Oh, okay.
好，等一下
Um, wait a minute.
不，汤玛士不要
不…拜托
Oh, no. Thomas, don't.
No, no, no.
不，汤玛士不要
不…拜托 我坚持!
Thomas, please, don't.
Uh... no, no. Uh, I insist.
算了吧
Please.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你爹说你
Your dad told me about, um...
不想再当褓母
you not wanting
to baby-sit anymore.
没有小孩看了
There's no baby to sit.
我只要你知道我了解
Well, I just want you
to know, I understand.
了解什么?
Understand what?
这一切是有一点怪异
That this might all seem
a little weird.
有一点?
A little?
我们想谢谢你，崔西
为什么?
I just want to thank you, Tracey.
For what?
你一直很有耐心
You've been very patient.
还有
And, uh...
你若认为时候到了我会了解
if you think the time has come
for this to end, then I understand.
谢谢你
Thank you.
晚安，佛兰西
Good night, Francis.
他从桌边叫我跳舞
你想想办法
He-He-He calls me from a table to dance.
Of course I expect you to do something.
汀克莉娜
他跟着这家伙进厕所
Christina, And then,And then, he
follows this guy to the washroom...
告诉这人他曾是我爱人
他曾经是
and he tells this guy that, that he was my lover.
Well, he was.
太过分了，佐儿
It's going too far, Zoe.
宝贝，你不知这有多过分
Actually, baby, you have
no idea how far it's gone.
我叫他摸你
You know, I told him to touch you.
我说你喜欢那样
I said you were into it. Yeah.
以前看你为他起舞
看你使他感到安慰
It used to be wonderful watching you dance
for him, seeing how you could soothe him.
我也高兴
I mean, it soothed me.
你使我得到安慰
You know, you soothed me.
懂吗?
Do you understand that?
不，不要
Hey, hey.
Don't, don't, don't!
别碰，混旦
Stop. Stop that!
Don't fucking touch me, you fucker!
住手,住手
不，滚开，佐儿
Stop!
Just fuck off, Zoe!
停手，艾瑞克
Stop it when I say! Eric!
Stop it! Ow!
冷静点
Chill out! Chill out!
冷静点 放松
Chill out! Relax!
好了 放松
艾瑞克，过来
All right? Relax!
Eric, come here!
约翰，滚出去
怎样回事? 不
John! Get out. What's the matter?
No!
滚开，佐儿！不
Fuck off, Zoe! No!
早安，汤玛土
Morning, Thomas.
怎么回事?
我得走了
What happened?
I had to leave.
你听到一切了吗?
Did you, uh, hear everything?
对
Yeah.
你知道吗?
Did you know?
我知道什么？
Did I know what?
她知道你女儿的事?
That she knew...
about your daughter.
警方侦讯我的
You know, when the,
when the police came to question me...
告诉我许多事
they told me
a lot of things.
他们说我妻和我弟有染
They told me that my wife
was having an affair with my brother;
已经数年之久
had been for years.
他们说我认为莉莎不是我女儿
They told me that I thought
Lisa wasn't my daughter.
他们说我以为她是哈洛生的
They told me
I thought she was Harold's.
他们为何那样说?
Wh-Why would they say that?
因为他们以为我会伤害她
Because they thought
I could harm her...
我会伤害她
that I would harm her.
后来他们找到真凶
And then they found the man
that, uh, that did it.
才放了我
Let me go.
我回到家中
And I went home.
数月后我妻因车祸丧生
And then my wife was killed
in a car accident a couple months later.
哈洛在车内
And, uh, Harold was in the car.
他没死
He lived.
你认为...
What do you think
it would have taken...
你父亲怎样才会杀人?
for your father
to kill someone?
我问这问题是因为我想杀个人
I'm asking because there's
someone that I want to kill now.
我昨夜在厕所听到他声音
I felt it last night
as I listened to him in the washroom.
我不懂
I don't understand.
他陷害我，叫我摸她
He set me up...
to touch her.
他为何那样做?
Why would he do that?
他夺走了我拥有的特别事物
He took something
very special from me.
我有许多的特别事物被人夺走
I've had too many
special things taken away.
所以我今晚必须回来
去杀他
That's why we have to go back tonight.
To kill him?
你会怎么做，汤玛士?
What would you do, Thomas?
What would you do? Well-
我会和他谈
我根本无法进去!
Well, I would talk to him.
I can't even get in there.
你会怎样?
What would you do?
今晚你回去
You go back tonight...
你叫她为你跳舞
and you have her
dance for you...
然后摸她
and then you touch her.
他会把你像我一样扔出去
And he'll throw you out
just like he threw me out.
但我会拿着枪在外面等他
But I'll be waiting outside
with the gun.
我不要帮你杀人
I'm not gonna
help you kill somebody.
不想少坐几年牢吗?
Not even to save
a few years in prison?
不
No.
帮我的忙吧?
Well, to help me then?
那是蜜拉，各位
And that was Mirella, gentlemen.
Mirella.
你只要花五元她会陪你坐台
You can have her at your own table
for only five dollars.
谢谢你，蜜拉
Thank you, Mirella.
很荣幸介绍下一位舞者
And now, it's always a pleasure
to announce to you our next dancer.
各位，鼓掌吧
Gentlemen, please, let's give
a big round of applause...
为克莉汀娜
for Christina.
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
我知道你的一切
I know everything about you.
你知道些什么?
What do you know about me?
我找到她
I found her.
你找到谁?
You found who?
你的小女孩
Your little girl.
噢 哦
Oh. Oh.
我找到她了，老兄
I found her, man.
我找到她了
I found her.
奏些快乐的曲子
Yeah, play something happy.
Play something happy.
嗨
Yeah. Hello.
喂?我去开
Okay, I'll get it,
I'll get it, I'll get it.
嗨,汀克莉娜
Hi, Christina.
Hi.
我来早了点
对，不要紧，进来
I'm a little bit early.
Yeah, th-that's okay. Come on in.
我不知道
Yeah, I mean,
it's difficult for me to tell...
我不太懂音乐
'cause I never had much
of a musical education myself...
但她老师认为她有天赋
but her teacher thinks
she's really talented.
我们想买架更好的钢琴给她
And, um, actually, we were thinking
of buying her a better piano.
很特别的大婴儿
An exotic baby grand,
you know?
我说大婴儿后她怎么说?
And when I mentioned "baby grand,"
do you know what she said to me?
她说爹那不是自相矛盾吗?
She said, "Dad,
isn't that a contradiction in terms?"
她一再使我感到惊奇
I mean, she just never
ceases to amaze me.
她才八岁，你相信吗?
I mean, she's eight years old.
Can you imagine?
她已经认识，你叫什么?
She can already identify-
Wh-What do you call that when...
名有两个
要说哪个？
it's two words,
kind of cancel each other out?
我感到惊奇
Oh, she just amazes me.
你在想什么?
Where's your mind?
我只是在想
I was just thinking.
想什么?
About what?
你谈论莉莎的方式
About the way
you talk about Lisa.
你变得好兴奋
You get so excited.
真好
It's nice.
我想你父母也会这样谈论你
Well, I'm sure your parents
talk about you that way too.
我不以为然
I don't think so.
我想会的
Oh, I do.
为什么?
Why?
因为你是负责的少女
Because you're a very
responsible young woman.
向什么负责?
Responsible to what?
向你相信你该做的事
Well, to whatever it is
you believe you have to do.
例如什么?
Like what?
莉莎很喜欢你作她褓母
Well, Lisa loves it when you
come over to baby-sit, for example.
她说你真会听她的话
She says you really
listen to her.
很好
That's nice.
她也听我说的话
She really listens
to me too.
她认为你不快乐
She thinks you're not very happy.
听我说，克莉汀娜
Listen, Christina,
如果你有事情想要谈一谈
if there's, if there's ever anything
you want to talk about...
谈家里什么的事
about what might be going on
at home or whatever...
我愿意倾听，好吗?
you know that I'm here, okay?
好的
好吗?
Okay.
Okay?
好的
Okay.
不，不要紧
Oh, no.
It's okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我真喜欢你送我回家
You know, I really enjoy
these drives home, Mr. Brown.
好，我也是
Good, good.
So do I.
再见，布朗先生
Bye, Mr. Brown.
Good-bye.